Guide to the Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
- Series VI: Burlington, Vermont
  - "Balancing Community and Nation." Building Economic Alternatives: Self-Reliant Community Development; A Quarterly Publication of CO-OP America., Winter 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    3 copies. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Freundlich, Paul.
  - "Burlington, Vermont: Laboratory for Change". Building Economic Alternatives: Self-Reliant Community Development; A Quarterly Publication of CO-OP America., Winter 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    3 copies. Photocopy. 3 pages. -- Author: Harold, Roberta A.
  - "Communities Force Banks to Re-invest". Building Economic Alternatives: Self-Reliant Community Development; A Quarterly Publication of CO-OP America., Winter 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    4 copies. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Wall, Kennington.
  - "Equity Common Thread at Wild Oats". The Burlington Free Press., Nov. 26, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Burlington Revolving Loan Program (BRLP): A Program Designed to Aid and Support the City of Burlington's Small Business Sector. Community and Economic Development Office (CEDO). (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Original Publication. Information Pamphlet. -- Author:
  - Bruce Seifer - Assistant Director for Economic Development, Community & Economic Development Office (CEDO). (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Business Card. -- Author: Seifer, Bruce
  - The Burlington Community Land Trust As A Private Complement To Public Land And Housing Programs: A Policy Proposal. Community and Economic Development Office (CEDO)., Sept., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    5 copies. Photocopy. 12 pages. -- Author: Davis, John.
  - Community & Economic Development Office (CEDO). Packet of City of Burlington Ordinances, Policy Summaries, Mission Statement and Memo to Pierre Clavel: from CEDO Office: Re: "Progressive Housing Policies in Burlington.", Feb. 1, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Photocopy. 85 pages. -- Author:
  - CEDO. Housing Packet to Pierre Clavel., Jan. 21, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Memo Sent to Pierre Clavel from CEDO Office in Burlington, Vermont. RE: "Burlington's Old North End (ONE)." (Box 9, Folder 5)
    4 copies. Photocopy. 15 page. -- Author:
  - Old North End Action Planning Process. ONE Building Community. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Equitable & Sustainable Community Development for Municipal Governments, State Governments, & Nonprofit Organizations. Burlington Associates in Community Development, Unknown (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "A City Supports Worker Ownership: Burlington, VT". Changing Work: A Magazine About Liberating Worklife., Spring 1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 3 pages. -- Author: Clavelle, Peter.
  - ICA Preliminary Analysis of Important Socio-Economic Trends in City of Burlington. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Executive Summary: Preliminary Analysis of Important Socio-Economic Trends in the City of Burlington, Vermont. Industrial Cooperative Association (ICA), Inc., Oct. 3, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Photocopy. 105 pages. -- Author:
  - Some Common Questions About Employee Ownership. Industrial Cooperative Association (ICA), Inc. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Burlington Progressive Coalition - Statement of Purpose (Draft). (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Burlington's Progressive Housing Program: The Record To Date (January 1988)., Jan. 1, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    4 copies. Photocopy. 6 pages. -- Author:
  - City of Burlington: Problem Overview; Creation of the Community and Economic Development Office; Overview of Activities to Date; Waterfront Development; Miscellaneous Activities., June 5, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Resolution Relating to Creating The Community and Economic Development Office (C.E.D.O.). The City of Burlington, Vermont., May 23, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Burlington Urban Design Study. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "Burlington, Vt. Divided by mayor's Tax Mission." The New York Times., Oct. 18, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - City of Burlington, Waterfront. Ten Year Conceptual Plan: A Revitalization Strategy for the 1990's and Beyond., July 31, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Original Bound Publication. 21 pages. -- Author:
  - The Burlington Women's Council Issues and Publications. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - The Burlington Women's Council. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Equity Common Thread at Wild Oats." Burlington Free Press, p. 4B., Nov. 26, 1986. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Burlington Women's Council Network News., June 9, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    2 copies. Original Newsletter. 3 pages. -- Author:
  - "Help Put an End to Sexual Assault..." (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Burlington Youth Office Documents (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Final Report: Support Systems and Youth. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Photocopy. 17 pages. -- Author: Driscoll, Jane
  - Memo. To Mayor Sanders and the Board of Aldermen. From Jane Driscoll, Youth Coordinator. Re: Youth Office Report. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Photocopy. 11 pages. -- Author: Driscoll, Jane
  - Subcommittee on Support Systems and Youth. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Photocopy. 15 pages. -- Author: Driscoll, Jane
  - Personal Letter to Members of the Board. From Jane Driscoll, Youth Coordinator. Re: Funding Needs. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Photocopy. 24 pages. -- Author: Driscoll, Jane
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. Fiscal Year 1987 Budget: Plans, Programs, Goals, and Priorities., June 16, 1986. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    2 copies. Original Publication. 12 pages. -- Author:
  - City of Burlington. Fully Tally of 227 Waterfront Surveys. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Photocopy. 21 pages. -- Author:
  - GBIC/CYNOSURE Marks Quarter Century." Burlington Free Press., Nov. 9, 1979. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Original Newsprint. 4 pages. -- Author:
  - Solidarity Newsletter: An Experiment in Co-publication of Newsletters of Progressive Groups in the Burlington Area. Vol. 2, No. 2., June 1982. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Greater Burlington Vermont Publications. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Greater Burlington Vermont: Where the business environment matches the quality of life. Greater Burlington Industrial Cooperation. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Original Bound Publication. 11 pages. -- Author:
  - Directory of Manufacturers., Jan. 1984. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Chittenden County, Vermont. A Profile of Life in a Special Community., Jan. 1983. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Original Bound Publication. 3 pages. -- Author:
  - Greater Burlington Vermont. Statistical Data. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Original Publication. 39 pages. -- Author:
  - City of Burlington. Housing Policy Documents. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Mission Statement CEDO Housing. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Burlington Housing Policy, 1984-1986., Dec. 5, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Operations Reviews: Burlington Nonprofit Housing System. Final Report. Prepared by Stockard & Engler & Brigham., Jan. 12, 1996. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Photocopy. 33 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington Housing Policy., Apr. 1997. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 27 pages. -- Author:
  - Enhancing the Viability of Burlington's Nonprofit Housing Delivery System: A Tentative Plan., Aug. 15, 1995. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Affordable Housing: The Seven Deadly Sins of Political Rhetoric. Progressive Coalition., Summer 1989. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Photocopy. 2 pages. -- Author: Davis, John.
  - City of Burlington. CEDO's Summaries, Fiscal and Annual Reports. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. Five Year Summary Report, 1983-1988. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    3 copies. Original and Photocopy. 40 pages. -- Author:
  - City of Burlington. Annual Report 1983., June 5, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Original Bound Publication. 100 pages. -- Author:
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. 1984 Report., Oct., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Original Bound Publication. 12 pages. -- Author:
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. 1986 Annual Report., Sept., 1986. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    2 copies. Original Bound Publication. 8 pages. -- Author:
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. 1987 Annual Report. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    3 copies. Original Bound Publication. 8 pages. -- Author:
  - CEDO's Fiscal Year 1987 Work Program. Memo To Mayor Bernard Sanders and Burlington Board of Aldermen. From Peter A. Clavelle, CEDO Director., June 12, 1986. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Photocopy. 10 pages. -- Author: Clavelle, Peter.
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. 1987 Annual Report., June 11, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Original Bound Publication. 7 pages. -- Author:
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. 1992 Annual Report., June 14, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Original Bound Publication. 18 pages. -- Author:
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. Annual Report., July 1995-June 1996. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Photocopy. 8 pages. -- Author:
  - Community and Economic Development in the City of Burlington, Vermont: A Progressive Agenda. And Progressive Program Information. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Community and Economic Development in the City of Burlington, Vermont: A Progressive Agenda., July, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 30 pages. -- Author:
  - Housing Improvement Program: Outline. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Photocopy. 10 pages. -- Author:
  - Community and Economic Development Office. Home Improvement Program. Fact Sheet. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - A Progressive Economic Development Program., Feb. 5, 1988. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Burlington's Progressive Housing Program: The Record to Date., Jan. 1988. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 6 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington's Progressive Housing Program., Dec. 2, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Community Development in Burlington, VT: Innovation, Participation, and Action. A Report presented to Mayor Peter Clavelle, City of Burlington., Apr. 6, 1988. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Photocopy. 45 pages. -- Author: Blosveren, Josh, Paul Edelstein, Amy Guptill and Arthur Rodgers.
  - Creating a Sustainable City: The Case of Burlington, Vermont. Prepared for the Mayor of Burlington's Office. Burlington, Vermont., May 5, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Original Bound. 45 pages. -- Author: Brown, Joshua.
  - "Burlington, Vermont - the nation's most sustainable city." Advertisement for the Committee to Re-Elect Peter Clavelle. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    2 copies. Original Newsprint. 2 pages. -- Author:
  - Course Readings for Politics in the People's Republic of Burlington. Instructor: Sue Burton. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Photocopies. 13 pages. -- Author: Burton, Sue
  - Affordable Housing Task Force: Report and Recommendations, 1985-1986. City of Burlington, VT. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    2 copies. Original Bound Publications. 36 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington College Political Questionnaire Collection. (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - City Republican Party Chair., Feb. 14, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    2 copies Photocopies. 17 pages. -- Author:
  - City Democratic Party Chair., Feb. 20, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    2 copies Photocopies. 19 pages. -- Author:
  - Citizen's Party Co-Chair., Feb. 28, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    2 copies Photocopies. 24 pages. -- Author:
  - Independent., Feb. 27, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Photocopy. 22 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington Election Candidates., Mar. 20-27, 1983. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Burlington Key Documents. Progressive City: Burlington. CRP 315 Packet. Miscellaneous. Compendiums compiled by Pierre Clavel, Sharon Lord and Tom Clavel (only Key Documents)., July 1989. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    -- Author: Clavel, Pierre, Sharon Lord and Tom Clavel
  - Annual Report: Mayor's Youth Office., Jan. 1983. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 3 pages. -- Author: Driscoll, Jane.
  - Mayor's Office on Women. Report to CEDO: Boom Pie Ordinance., Mar. 1985. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 4 pages. -- Author:
  - "Party Talk." Vanguard Press., Mar. 3-10, 1985. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 4 pages. -- Author: Dillon, John and Gail Hudson.
  - "Tax Crisis: No Magic Potions." Vanguard Press., June 23-30, 1985. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 3 pages. -- Author: Letzelter-Smith, Peter.
  - Vanguard Press. "Yes" position by Marty Jezer, "No" position by Hamilton Davis., Apr. 6-13, 1986. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 3 pages. -- Author: Should Bernie Run?
  - "Waterfront Dealing." Vanguard Press., Oct. 19-26, 1986. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 4 pages. -- Author: Freyne, Peter.
  - "Second Wind for the Sanderistas." Vanguard Press., Mar. 8-15, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 3 pages. -- Author: Freyne, Peter.
  - "Identity Crisis." Vanguard Press., Mar. 22-29, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 3 pages. -- Author: Rice, Tom.
  - "The Progressive Reaction." Vanguard Press., Mar. 22-29, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 1 page. -- Author: Freyne, Peter.
  - "Taking it to the Courts." Vanguard Press., May 17-24, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 2 pages. -- Author: Marnis, Joshua.
  - "The Return of the Boogey-Man." Vanguard Press., Oct. 22-29, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 2 pages. -- Author: Johnson, Mark.
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. "A Progressive Housing Program.", Dec. 2, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 2 pages. -- Author:
  - "A Profile of the Burlington Community Land Trust." Vanguard Press., Apr. 28-May 5, 1988. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 3 pages. -- Author: Lechner, Sheryl.
  - City of Burlington, Community and Economic Development Office. "Five Year Summary Report, 1983-1988." (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Original in Key Documents Bound Publication. 40 pages. -- Author:
  - "Two Cheers for Progs." Vanguard Press., Mar. 9-16, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 3 pages. -- Author: Kelly, Kevin.
  - "Eight Years that Shook Vermont." Vanguard Press., Mar. 16-23, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Key Documents Bound Publication. 3 pages. -- Author: Guma, Greg.
  - A Progressive City: Burlington. Preface and List of Documents., Feb. 1, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Progressive City Bound Publication. 4 pages. -- Author:
  - Memo to CRP 315. From Pierre Clavel and Sharon Lord., Feb. 2, 1988. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Burlington Packet Compilation. 2 pages. -- Author: Clavel, Pierre and Sharon Lord
  - Demographics - Population and Housing Change. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Burlington Packet Compilation. 1 page. -- Author:
  - "Burlington Loves Bernie." In These Times., Mar., 1983. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Burlington Packet Compilation. 6 pages. -- Author: Moberg, David.
  - "Socialism in One City?" Socialist Review., Dec. 1986. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Burlington Packet Compilation. 11 pages. -- Author: Bookchin, Murray.
  - Community Land Trust. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Burlington Packet Compilation. 8 pages. -- Author:
  - Organizing to Cary Out Community and Economic Development. (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Small Business Revolving Loan Fund. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Copy in Burlington Packet Compilation. 3 pages. -- Author:
  - Mayoral Campaign - 1988/89. Press Releases. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Photocopy. 9 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington Contacts. (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Trudeam, GB. Doonesbury. (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Murray for Mayor Ads. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author:
  - Innovations in State and Local Government: 1991 Awards Program. Semifinalist Application. Signed by Michael Monte (CEDO Director) and Peter Clavelle (Mayor)., Mar. 29, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Photocopy with Handwritten Note. 7 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington Bibliography. (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Photocopies. Handwritten Notes. 21 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington Chronology. (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Photocopies. 4 pages. -- Author:
  - "Burlington Since the 1930's: Change and Continuity in Vermont's Largest City." p. 52-62 (in unknown source). (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Photocopies. 5 pages. -- Author: Johnson, Clark.
  - Acquisition of Waterfront Properties: Report and Recommendations. Submitted to City Council, City of Burlington., Jan. 1988. (Box 9, Folder 33)
    Original Bound Publication. 44 pages. -- Author: Baker, Sidney C., Peter A. Clavelle and Mark Eldridge.
  - Annual City Report, 1981. City of Burlington, VT., June 3, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Original Bound Publication. 238 pages. -- Author:
  - Why the Greens Challenged the Progressives in Burlington, Vermont., June 1, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Photocopy. 2 pages. -- Author: Baird, Sandra.
  - Joan Beauchemin Correspondence. (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Personal Letter to Pierre Clavel., Mar. 18, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Typescript. 2 pages. -- Author: Beauchemin, Joan
  - Loh, Jules, "Novel Approach to Downtown Renovation Works for Amish." The Burlington Free Press, p. 6A. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Beauchemin, Joan
  - Re-Elect Bernie Sanders, Independent for Mayor. Mayor Bernie Sanders...Working hard to keep Burlington a great place to live. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Original Leaflet. 1 page. -- Author: Beauchemin, Joan
  - Mass mailing: letter from Bernard Sanders. Sanders for Governor. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Original Letter. 1 page. -- Author: Beauchemin, Joan
  - "Socialism in One City?" Socialist Review. (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - "The Bernie Sanders Paradox: When Socialism Grows Old." p. 51-62. (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Photocopy. 6 pages. -- Author: Bookchin, Murray.
  - "Dilemmas of Socialism on the West Coast of New England." p.62-66. (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Photocopy. 2 pages. -- Author: Higgins, Bryan R.
  - "Response." p. 66-70. (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Photocopy. 3 pages. -- Author: Bookchin, Muray.
  - Burlington City Planning Commission - An Overview., Dec. 1981. (Box 9, Folder 38)
    Photocopy. 20 pages. -- Author:
  - Strategies for local Ownership and Control: A Policy Analysis. Industrial Cooperative Association, Inc. Somerville, MA., Jan. 1983. (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Original Bound Publication. 31 pages. -- Author: Mackin, Christopher.
  - Franco Jr., John L., John Howland, Jr., Rosaire J. Longe (ex officio), Robert C. Sweeney and Dr. Jennie V. Stoler (Chair). Report of the Mayor's Committee on Taxation. Submitted to Bernard Sanders, Mayor. City of Burlington., Dec. 1981. (Box 9, Folder 40)
    4 copies. Photocopies. 26 pages. -- Author: Stoler, Jennie V.
  - Mayor's Council on Women. Report. (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Project Self-Sufficiency Action Plan. Community and Economic Development Office. Burlington, VT., Jan., 1984. (Box 9, Folder 42)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 11 pages. -- Author:
  - Project Self-Sufficiency Questions and Answers. Community and Economic Development Office. Burlington, VT., Jan., 1984. (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Photocopy. 4 ages. -- Author:
  - Small Business Burlington Revolving Loan Program (BRLP). Fact Sheet. Community and Economic Development Office. Burlington, VT. (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Photocopy. 3 pages -- Author:
  - A Study of Public Access and Improvements for the Burlington Waterfront. Prepared for the Office of Community and Economic Development., Sept. 25, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    2 copies. Original Bound Publication. 55 pages. -- Author: Kielman, Rolf, Roland Batten, Turner Brooks, Peter Owens and Elizabeth Humstone.
  - The Municipal Development Plan for the City of Burlington. Draft. Planning Commission: Burlington, VT., Mar. 15, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 19 pages. -- Author:
  - Ward of the Neighborhood Planning Assembly Information and Updates. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Ward One: Neighborhood Planning Assembly Bylaws., Oct. 19, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Photocopies. 16 pages. -- Author:
  - "Neighborhood Bulletin Board: Neighborhood Assemblies Move Out of Limbo." Burlington Citizen, p. 4., Aug., 1983. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - "Local Assemblies Update." Burlington Citizen, p. 4., Sept. 1983. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - "Assembly Update." Burlington Citizen, p. 4., Nov., 1983. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - "Neighborhood Bulletin Board: Neighborhood Planning Update." Burlington Citizen, p. 4., Oct., 1983. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - "Neighborhood Bulletin Board: Assembly Update." Burlington Citizen, p. 2., Jan., 1984. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - City of Burlington. Resolution., June 4, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Ward II Voice: Newsletter of the Ward II Neighborhood Assembly. Vol. I, No. 5., June, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Original Copy. 4 pages. -- Author:
  - Official Election Results: City of Burlington., Mar. 1, 1983. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - The People's Guide to Burlington's City Government. City of Burlington: City Clerk's Office., Oct. 29, 1985. (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Original Newsprint. 13 pages. -- Author:
  - Preliminary Report to Mayor Bernard Sanders from the Mayor's Committee on the Arts. Burlington, VT., June 3, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 16 pages. -- Author: Abair, Alan, Paul Schnobble and Adam Zahler (Chairmen).
  - BCLT Annual Report, Pamphlets, Flyers. (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - The Champlain Valley Mutual Housing Federation: Program and Services Summary. The Burlington Area Cooperative Housing Federation. (Box 9, Folder 49)
    Original Pamphlet. 1 page. -- Author:
  - HOMELAND. Burlington Community Land Trust. (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Annual Reports for Fiscal Year 1997. A Banner Year for the Burlington Community Land Trust and the Champlain Valley Mutual Housing Federation. The Burlington Land Trust and the Champlain Valley Mutual Housing Federation., June 19, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    Original Bound Publication. 13 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington Community Land Trust News. Vol. 10, Nos. 1., Sprint 1996 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    Original Publication. 3 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington Community Land Trust News. Vol. 10, Nos. 3 & 4., Fall/Winter 1996 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    2 copies. Original Publication. 4 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington Community Land Trust News. Vol. 11, Nos. 3., Summer 1997. (Box 9, Folder 49)
    Original Publication. 6 pages. -- Author:
  - Burlington Community Land Trust News. Vol. 12, Nos. 1., Fall 1997-Winter 1997/98 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Burlington Community Land Trust: Homes for Sale. Listings., Jan. 20, 1998. (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Burlington Community Land Trust: The BCLT Lease and You. (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Economic Consulting Services. Final Report. A Feasibility Study to Evaluate the Opportunity for a Community Development Corporation (CDC) in Burlington, Vermont. Prepared for City of Burlington Community and Economic Development Office (CEDO) and Champlain Valley Office of Economic Opportunity (CVOEO)., Mar. 6, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    Photocopy. 51 pages. -- Author:
  - "Burlington, Northern Light." The Nation, p. 19-20, 23., May 19, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 51)
    Photocopy. 3pages. -- Author: Walljasper, Jay.
  - "Burlington Seeking U.S. Grant To Revitalize 3 Neighborhoods". The Burlington Free Press., Aug. 20, 1980 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; City Finances section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author:
  - "City Could Save $100,000 On Insurance, Report Says". The Burlington Free Press., Apr. 14, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; City Finances section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: MacKay, Scott.
  - "Board OKs Plan to Save $200,000 on Insurance". The Burlington Free Press., Jun. 30, 1982 (Box 9)
    Bound Collection of Articles; City Finances section. Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Melvin, Don.